

# NIKITA SHEVCHUK

## · CONTACTS ·

Kyiv Ukraine +380931471176 shevchuk.nikita.gh@gmail.com

## SKILLS

JavaScript, Typescript

React.js

Redux, Redux Toolkit, MobX

GitHub, Git

Node js

HTML & CSS (SASS, SCSS)

Unit testing (Jest)

npm, yarn (package management with node.js)

Material UI (for React.js)

**Bootstrap** 

JQuery

Figma, Photoshop

Other libraries: Formik, Final-form, React-Router, Lodash, Axios, Swiper, qs

## LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate (B1)

Ukrainian - Native

# ° LINKS °

Github

(https://github.com/NikitaShevchuk)

<u>LinkedIn</u> (https://cutt.ly/N1PzwHc)

#### SUMMARY

Software engineer with freelance experience. Can easily communicate in English during workflow. Have got a hands-on experience with React. Ready to develop software engineering skills with React and Angular to bring the best solution for a client. See my personal portfolio website: https://nikitashevchuk.github.io/portfolio/

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Freelance

June 2020 — December 2021

- Developed a resource for publishing and downloading articles and books in different formats.
- Provided an online service to customer for searching and managing different schools and courses for children.
- Made more than 10 websites with HTML/CSS, Javascript and Wordpress.
  See full list of websites made by me (2020-2021) and customers feedback: https://cutt.ly/gBIcjnA

## ★ PROJECTS

### Social Network For Developers

February 2022 — May 2022

- Try in use: https://nikitashevchuk.github.io/my-app
- Repository: https://github.com/NikitaShevchuk/my-app

With this app you can find developers, text in common developers chat, add people to friends list and also text a private messages.

· Technologies: react, redux, redux-thunk, typerscript

# Online clothing store

June 2022 — September 2022

- Try in use: https://nikitashevchuk.github.io/e-commerce
- Repository: https://github.com/NikitaShevchuk/e-commerce

Online store application. You can easy find a product you want with filters, sorting and search.

• Technologies: react, redux toolkit, RTK Query, Material UI

#### My personal portfolio app

• Repository: https://github.com/NikitaShevchuk/portfolio

Technologies: react, mobx

## EDUCATION

Software Engineering, National Taras Shevchenko University of Kiev (Optical and Mechanical College), Kyiv

August 2019 — May 2023

## COURSES

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), by Maximilian Schwarzmüller - udemy.com

The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert!, , by Jonas Schmedtmann - udemy.com